<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<words>
  <word>
    <original>have green fingers</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>to be good at gardening and making plants grow well</translation>
      <translation>My mom can keep any plant alive, even ones that I've nearly killed—she seriously has green fingers.</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>bookworm</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>someone who enjoys reading very much</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>math wiz(ard)</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>someone who is very good at math (or something else)</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>be/feel under the weather</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>to feel ill</translation>
      <translation>I noticed that the cat was looking a little under the weather.</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>sit on the fence</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>avoid deciding between two sides</translation>
      <translation>The government has been sitting on the fence about legalizing marijuana for the past several years.</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>jump on the bandwagon</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>to join or follow something once it is successful or popular</translation>
      <translation>I can't stand these people who just jump on the bandwagon after a win. Where were they last year when the team was terrible?</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>beat about the bush</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>take too long before saying what you want to say; avoid saying something directly</translation>
      <translation>Don’t beat about the bush. Tell me exactly what you think is wrong with my work.</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>couch potato</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>lazy and spend most of their time sitting, watching TV</translation>
      <translation>Most evenings they sit, like a pair of couch potatoes in front of television.</translation>
      <translation>Most of these people are junk-food eating couch potatoes.</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>nosy parker</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>someone who wants to know too much about other people</translation>
      <translation>Our next door neighbour is a real nosy parker.</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>miss the boat</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>to lose the chance or opportunity to do something</translation>
      <translation>If you don't call the recruiter back right away, you're going to miss the boat</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>get/have butterflies in (one's) stomach</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>to have a feeling of nervousness, often before a performance or undertaking of some kind</translation>
      <translation>I almost didn't go on stage and perform tonight because I had butterflies in my stomach.</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
  <word>
    <original>hot potato</original>
    <translations>
      <translation>it is very difficult to deal with, especially because it is something that people argue about a lot</translation>
      <translation>His resignation is a political hot potato.</translation>
    </translations>
  </word>
</words>